Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Records Concerning the Archives 300 Project
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, records concerning the Archives 300 Project
1983-2001
RU 885
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
4.42
The records consist of administrative files and the Yale Archives 300 project web site [computer files] documenting the project initiatives, staff, and history.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-D (YRG 32-D), Records of Yale school and departmental libraries and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Biographical / Historical
Archives 300 was a five-year, University-sponsored project which enabled the Yale University Archives to carry out and extend its mission to document, preserve, and support research on Yale history, accomplishments, and contributions.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of administrative files and the Yale Archives 300 project web site [computer files] documenting the project initiatives, staff, and history.
Archives; Libraries -- Special collections; Computer files; Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Web site for the Archives 300 Project [computer files], 1998-2000; Accession 2003-A-149
  - Archives 300 project web site, 1998-2000; 41 computer files (HTML, JPG, GIF)
  - Archives 300 project web site, 2000; 115 computer files (HTML, JPG, GIF)
- Archives 300 records, including background materials on office file keeping systems, 1983-2001; Accession 2006-A-224
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - Shredding documentation, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Records Management legal issues, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administrative history, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Records opening soon, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Staff meeting, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Project team meetings, 1998-1999, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Controller's office, 1998, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Biology department, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Central Human Resources, 1998, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Davenport College, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dwight Hall, 2000, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Librarian's office, 1983, 1993, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Career Services, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Yale College Dean's office, 1993, 1998, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - School of Drama, 1998, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Manuscripts and Archives, 1993, 1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Forestry School, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Provost's office, 1997-2001, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Students and Scholars, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Brewster presidential papers restrictions, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Other RM programs, 1995, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Records Center project, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Health records, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Office of origin permissions, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Facilities, 1995, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)